(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Charlie was going to visit a candy factory.
He was going with his parents.
On this trip, he would take a tour
of the factory.
He would be with other children and their
families.
At the end of the trip, they could
fill up one bag of candy they wanted.
He was very excited.
He was in a group with three other
families.
They took a tour of the factory.
They saw how the chocolate and candy were
made.
It was fascinating to see what happened before
it went into their mouths.
At the end of the trip, they each
got a plastic bag.
Charlie filled his up with sour candy, chocolate,
and soda candy.
He was very happy.